[
    {
        "question": "What is 1+1?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is Pikachu?",
        "answers": ["Yellow", "Green", "Blue", "Red"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Most people in Europe belong to what religion?",
        "answers": ["Judaism", "Islam", "Christianity", "Zorostrianism"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "What name is given to someone who is skeptical of the policies of the European Union?",
        "answers": ["Eurosceptic", "Eurovision", "Eurostar", "Eurotrash"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "The capital of France is what?",
        "answers": ["Bourges", "Nantes", "Strasbourg", "Paris"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is the name of Han Solo's spaceship in Star Wars?",
        "answers": ["Millenium Eagle", "Millenium Vulture", "Millenium Condor", "Millenium Falcon"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "The seat of the Church of England is in which city?",
        "answers": ["London", "Salisbury", "Canterbury", "Oxford"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [1, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles Ingram was associated with a Millionaire cheating scandal in which year?",
        "answers": ["2000", "2001", "2002", "2003"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jove is another name for which Roman god?",
        "answers": ["Neptune", "Jupiter", "Uranus", "Saturn"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Hindu god looks like an elephant?",
        "answers": ["Vishnu", "Hanuman", "Shiva", "Ganesh"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the 1984 film 'The Karate Kid', which of these is not the name of a Cobra Kai student?",
        "answers": ["Dutch", "Billy", "Tommy", "Jimmy"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these World War II battles came first, chronologically?",
        "answers": ["Battle of Okinawa", "D-Day", "Bombing of London", "Operation Barbarossa"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "The 1779 painting, 'The Blue Boy' by Thomas Gainsborough, depicts a boy holding what?",
        "answers": ["Bird", "Hat", "Stick", "Sword"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Hussites were a religious sect that emerged in the 15th century, in which country?",
        "answers": ["Poland", "Hungary", "Germany", "Czech Republic"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph and Marcel Lefebvre worked in the 20th century as what?",
        "answers": ["U.S politicians", "Catholic archbishops", "Television producers", "Business owners"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    }
]